[{"answer": " Hello, Stephanie.  Please come into my office.  Its nice to meet you", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Thank you.  Its nice to meet you too", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hello, Stephanie.  Please come into my office.  Its nice to meet you", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " So, youre here today to talk about the chairperson of a meeting, is that right", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Thank you.  Its nice to meet you too", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": "Um-hmm.  Thats right.  Actually, Im kind of new to the work world.  I jus", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 18, "question": " So, youre here today to talk about the chairperson of a meeting, is that right", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " And what do you do", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Um-hmm.  Thats right.  Actually, Im kind of new to the work world.  I jus", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": "Im an industrial designer with a large company", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 23, "question": " And what do you do", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " OK, interesting.  So, do you chair a lot of meetings", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 24, "question": "Im an industrial designer with a large company", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Well, thats why Im here.  Ive been to a lot of meetings, but Ive never bee", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 30, "question": " OK, interesting.  So, do you chair a lot of meetings", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": "Sure.  I can help you with that.  Actually, the chairperson is a really importan", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Well, thats why Im here.  Ive been to a lot of meetings, but Ive never bee", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Yeah, Ive heard its kind of a hard job, so I wanted to get some pointers", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Sure.  I can help you with that.  Actually, the chairperson is a really importan", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Well, basically the chairperson is the person who leads a meeting.  We can tal", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Yeah, Ive heard its kind of a hard job, so I wanted to get some pointers", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Well, basically the chairperson is the person who leads a meeting.  We can tal", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " So lets start with before the meeting.  The chairperson needs to be a", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 48, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " All right", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 53, "question": " So lets start with before the meeting.  The chairperson needs to be a", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": "The first thing the chairperson needs to do before the meeting is make sure tha", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 54, "question": " All right", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Would I just do that by email", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 60, "question": "The first thing the chairperson needs to do before the meeting is make sure tha", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Yes, thats the way its usually done.  Also, the chairperson needs to make sur", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Would I just do that by email", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Yes, thats the way its usually done.  Also, the chairperson needs to make sur", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " There are several tasks the chairperson has to do during the meeting as well", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 66, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " What about latecomers?  Should I wait for them", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 70, "question": " There are several tasks the chairperson has to do during the meeting as well", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " No, dont wait for anyone who is late.  The meeting should start on time.  Th", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 71, "question": " What about latecomers?  Should I wait for them", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": "Can I choose anyone", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 76, "question": " No, dont wait for anyone who is late.  The meeting should start on time.  Th", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " You can ask anyone you would like to do this.  Often its a secretary, but yo", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Can I choose anyone", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 84, "question": " You can ask anyone you would like to do this.  Often its a secretary, but yo", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": "The chairperson also needs to make sure that each point on the agenda is give", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 85, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Ive been to some really long meetings where that didnt happen", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 91, "question": "The chairperson also needs to make sure that each point on the agenda is give", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Unfortunately, that happens sometimes when the chairperson isnt doing thei", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Ive been to some really long meetings where that didnt happen", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Thats true", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Unfortunately, that happens sometimes when the chairperson isnt doing thei", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Finally, the chairperson also is responsible for diplomatically handling an", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Thats true", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Do they have to do anything after the meeting", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 102, "question": " Finally, the chairperson also is responsible for diplomatically handling an", "qSentId": 101},{"answer": " Yes, they do.  The chairperson should make sure that the minutes of th", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 103, "question": " Do they have to do anything after the meeting", "qSentId": 102},{"answer": " It sounds like the chairperson has a lot to do", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 108, "question": " Yes, they do.  The chairperson should make sure that the minutes of th", "qSentId": 107},{"answer": " They do have an important job at the meeting.  But, if you do it well, youll hav", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 109, "question": " It sounds like the chairperson has a lot to do", "qSentId": 108},{"answer": " Well, thank you for your time and explaining the role of the chairperson t", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 113, "question": " They do have an important job at the meeting.  But, if you do it well, youll hav", "qSentId": 112},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  I hope you do a great job next month", "docId": "03-10", "aSentId": 117, "question": " Well, thank you for your time and explaining the role of the chairperson t", "qSentId": 116}]
